http://www.iss.com/about/privacy.html

K2 – time-resolved spectrofluorometer
PC1 – photon counting spectrofluorometerQuanta – particle counter
Processing Electronics
Phoenix (SLM Upgrade)
Software
Vinci
Datan
Microscopy
Time-resolved Laser Scanning Confocal Microscopes (LSM)
Alba STED – Super-resolution Time-resolved LSM
Alba v5 – Time-resolved LSM with single-molecule sensitivity
PL1 – Photoluminescence Microscope for material research studiesQ2 – Modular LSM for FLIM and FCS
Privacy Policy
At ISS we recognize that your privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by ISS, Inc., its subsidiaries or affiliated organizations. We do not rent or sell personal information about you. You can visit the ISS website without revealing any personal information other than the information that is used in computer network transmissions. ISS will make some personal identification information available to a limited number of ISS subsidiaries or organizations for the purpose of meeting your request with the highest level of sales, customer service or support. Within the ISS website, you can browse products or services, make requests, download documentation, and navigate to other websites. The types of personal information collected on these pages include your name, email address, and interests in regards to our products and services. ISS will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the uses described above.
If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at Privacy Matters, c/o ISS Inc., 1602 Newton Drive, Champaign, Illinois, 61822 USA.
Use of Documentation
ISS is dedicated to provide innovative fluorescence instrumentation to scientists working in the life sciences, drug discovery, material sciences and basic physical-chemical research applications. Our fluorescence product line includes steady-state spectrofluorometers, spectrometers for the determination of multiple decay times, fluorescence microscopes, laser scanning confocal microscopes, a spectrometer for fluorescence correlation spectroscopy and a particle-tracking system for single molecule detection.
ISS has a long history of innovation and holds the relevant patents pertinent to frequency-domain instrumentation: ISS is the leader in frequency-domain time-resolved fluorescence instrumentation. ISS instruments share a series of interchangeable accessories covering a variety of applications; modular components allow the user to upgrade the instrumentation with novel capabilities as well as to assemble a custom-designed instrument. Instruments are designed with an open architecture from the excitation side to the collection channels; the excitation light sources of ISS instruments are xenon arc lamps, continuous wave lasers, laser diodes, light emitting diodes, multiphoton lasers and synchrotron radiation rings.
Disclaimer
ISS attempts to provide accurate information free of errors on this website; however, ISS assumes no responsibility should errors or inaccuracies occur. ISS reserves the right to change the content without notice and provides this website "as is" with no express or implied warranty. Mention of non-ISS products or links to third-party websites does not constitute an endorsement or recommendation. Furthermore, ISS shall not be responsible for any direct, indirect, special, consequential, incidental or punitive damages, including, without limitation, lost profits or revenues, costs of replacement or substitute goods, loss or damage to data arising out of the use or inability to use this website, or damages resulting from use of or reliance on the information present, even if ISS has been advised of the possibility of such damages.
Information Collection
We collect the information you give us in order to provide you services, inform you about our products and fulfill your user requests. We work with consumer marketing companies to help us better target our services and product communications to you.
Cookies
ISS may set and access cookies on your computer. As of the date of this document, this website does not use cookies.
User Submissions
ISS does not wish to receive any information that is considered confidential or proprietary via this website. In using this website, you agree that any information or materials provided to ISS will not be considered confidential or proprietary.
This website is maintained by ISS. It takes advantage of Javascript technologies. Please be sure to enable Javascript in your web browser to take full advantage of features on this website.
Please, enjoy the use of this site. Feel free to contact us with complaints, comments, or suggestions. This policy was last updated on January 29, 2008.
Learn More About ISS:
Copyright © 2020 ISS, Inc. All rights reserved. | Privacy Policy | Contact Us
